you have a type like this, if you look at
у вас типаж вот э Если Вы посмотрите там
Emelya’s fairy tales, for example, yes, the facial type
сказки Емеля например да вот типаж лица
was also depicted very similar to yours Yes,
тоже изображался очень похожий на ваш Да
well, I mixed it in, here
ну я подмешал вним вот у
I have Hello, I’m from the city of
меня Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky, where are you from? I’m from the city of Moscow, I
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я из города Москва
understand, but we ourselves are originally from the
понял а сами родом родом откуда из
Moscow region  No, I mean the
Московской области Не ну имею в виду
ancestors of Ryazan Ryazan because I
предки Рязань Рязань потому что вот я
see that you are either Udmurt by
вижу что вы либо удмурт по
nationality or not seriously Udmurt,
национальности либо не серьёзно удмурты
by the way, the most red-haired nation on the
кстати самая рыжеволосая нация на
planet Yes, I am aware and you
планете Да я в курсе да и у вас
also have an Udmurt anthropological type,
антропологический тип удмуртский тоже
you are anthropologists, I am an anthropologist, yes I am an
тяй вы антропологи я антрополог да я
anthropologist  My education
антрополог у меня образование
is Kyiv National
есть Киевский национальный университет
Taras Shevchenko University and 18 years of
имени Тараса Шевченко и 18 лет уже
practice already, in 2 years there will be a
практики через 2 года будет
twentieth university Kyiv
двадцатой университет Киевский
National Taras Shevchenko University
национальный университет имени Тараса
Taras Shevchenko National National University named after
университет имени Тараса Шевченко имени
Taras Shevchenko interesting Interesting
Тараса Шевченко интересно Интересно так
Well, I opened its Wikipedia page, I’ll
Ну я открыл её страницу Википедии
read it, and here you are  tell me,
почитаю пото вот а вы скажите а вы
instead of introducing yourself, instead of
вместо представления вместо того чтобы
giving your name, you immediately name the city
имя своё назвать вы сразу город
Yes, why is that and I want to
называете Да почему так а я хочу
identify Where is the person from
идентифицировать Откуда человек
and how are you? Well, what conclusions do you draw from
а а как вы Ну какие вы выводы делаете из
this? Well, for example, if a person lives in
этого Ну например если человек живёт в
Moscow, I can talk to him about one thing
Москве я с ним об одном могу поговорить
If  he’s in Vladivostok about something else I can
Если он во Владивостоке о другом могу
talk about, for example, there are different ones And
поговорить например там же разные А о
what do you prefer to talk about with people
чём вы предпочитаете общаться с людьми
from Moscow about different things But with you I’m
из Москвы о разном Но вот с вами Мне
interested in anthropology by the way because
интересно о антропологии кста потому что
well, you’re not quite the Moscow type of
ну вот вы довольно не Московский типаж
person If you Look what dadada yes I
лица Если вы Смотри что дадада да так
’m saying so  It’s quite a non-Moscow type of face
говорю довольно не Московский типаж лица
you have.
у Вас
Uh-huh If you look at this in Russian
Угу Если вы смотрите вот в русских
folk tales as they depicted
народных сказках так как изображали
Pern very often in pictures. I apologize, you
картинках перна Я прошу прощения вы
disappeared for a few seconds. Can you
пропали на несколько секунд Можете
repeat please? In Soviet
повторить пожалуйста вот в советское
times, you saw how the character was depicted in Russian folk
время вы видели как в русских народных
tales.
сказках изображали
Well, it happened  I saw Yes, I
персонажа Ну бывало видел Да у меня
had a lot of Soviet books Yes,
много было советских книжек Да вот
you can describe
Можете описать
him in two words No, I can’t, of course,
его а двумя словами Нет не могу конечно
not in two Here’s the head area of ​​the head
не не двумя Вот голову район головы
Describe Well, the trapezoid is an ordinary classic
Опишите Ну трапеция обычная классическая
The hair
Волосы
was usually light reddish Well,
какие светлые рыжеватые обычно были Ну
light reddish reddish If we
светлые рыжеватые рыжеватые Если мы
look there, the pictures had And  so
смотрим вот там картинки имели И так
on Yes, of course, we can’t say
дальше Да мы конечно не можем говорить
what happened before because this was the Soviet
что было раньше потому что это советское
era, that’s how the artists saw it, but
время это вот художники так видели да но
well, the Soviet era, in addition to the fact that they
ну советское время помимо того что
also depicted blond, blue-eyed people, they
изображали ещё и блондинов голубоглазых
also depicted the Chinese. Well, Asians, I
ещё изображали китайцев Ну азиатов
mean Negroids and there Negroids,
имеется в виду негроидов и там негроидов
and so on.  therefore, they depicted
и так далее вот поэтому изображали
different people in Russian folk tales,
разных людей в руских народных сказках
stinging the Chinese and Negroids at the blockades at the
жали китайцев и негроидов на блокадах на
blockades. I mean, I mean about
блокадах Я име виду я имею виду про
fairy tales, so look. The fact is that
сказки так вот смотрите Дело в том что
this type of Russian folk tales,
вот этот типаж русских народных сказок
so if you looked, was
так если вы э смотрели был
Uh,
Ээ
in the thirties, back under Stalin  when the
в тридцатых годах ещё при Сталине когда
domestic publishing house was formed
формировалось отечественное издательство
so uh it was in, if I’m not mistaken, in Moscow
так ээ был в если я не ошибаюсь в Москве
or in Leningrad, but I can’t
или в Ленинграде вот я не могу
be sure exactly where it was,
точно быть уверен где это был
yes, the Union for
да Союз
the Study of Russian Anthropology. It was
изучения российской антропологии Вот его
somehow later renamed in Soviet style,
как-то потом переименовали по-советски
there with antr And so on.  and they
вот там со антр И так дальше Вот и они
collected types of people from different regions
собирали с разных регионов типажи типажи
And this is the type that
людей И вот тот типаж который пошёл
later went into Russian folk tales, it comes
потом в русские народные сказки он идёт
from the Perm region of Udmurtia and Mordovia
с Пермского края Удмуртии и Мордовии
from the Perm region of Udmurtia, Moldova, and
с Пермского края Удмуртии молдови так
Mordovia. You have a type, if you
Мордовии Вот вы у вас типаж вот если Вы
look at Emel’s tales there, for example, yes,  the
посмотрите там сказки Емеля например да
type of face was also depicted very
вот типаж лица тоже изображался очень
similar to yours Yes, well, I mixed in some
похожий на ваш Да ну я подмешал вот у
substitutions and a little Slav So
меня подмены и славянин немножечко Так
who is substituting with whom you have with the Tatars
кто с кем подмены у вас с татарами
the Slavs with the Tatars So, well,
славяне с татарами Так а ну а татари
where did
откуда у
you get the Tatars from now I can’t say I’m not with that
вас вот сейчас не могу сказать Я с той
part of the family  especially In principle,
частью семьи не особо В принципе знаком
I’m familiar, well, at least approximately
я ну ну хотя хотя бы приблизительно
the region Well, Tatarstan, the thing is that
регион Ну Татарстан дело дело в том что
look,
смотрите
uh, your appearance is definitely not Tatar. The
ээ у вас внешность точно не татарская
fact is that when there was an ox,
Дело в том что вот когда была вол
Bulgaria, you know, there was such a state,
Булгария знаете такая был государство
no. But the fact is that on the territory of
нет А дело в том что на территории
modern there  Chuvash and Tatarstan And
современного там Чуваши и Татарстана И
so on there was the state of Volga
так дальше было государство Волжское
Bulgaria, a very strong state
Булгария вот очень сильное государство
they were, uh, you can go to these territories. Yes,
было они ээ в эти территории можете Да
google it, take Volga Bulgaria
загуглите вот Возьмите Волжская Булгария
Yes, yes, I’m just looking at the same time, you
Да да да я просто параллельно смотрю вы
can say yes, it included
можете говорить да э туда входили
tribes of both the Mari and the Udmurts, and so
племена и марийцев и удмуртов и так
on, yes  that is, most likely your
дальше да то есть скорее всего ваши
ancestors, they may be from Tatarstan, but they are not
предки они может из Татарстана но они не
Tatars, they are Udmurts who, uh, so to
татары они э удмурты которые Ээ как бы
speak, Otari, you can say yes, either they
так сказать Отари можно сказать да либо
just lived in Tatarstan, or Well, they
просто жили в Татарстане либо Ну они
were Muslims, these are your ancestors or
мусульмане были вот эти ваши предки или
just Tatars, no, no, not in  I’m
просто татары не-не не в у меня
Muslim, at least as far as I
мусульман по крайней мере насколько я
can trace my
могу проследить своё родословно
Muslim ancestry. I don’t have that. That is,
мусульман У меня нету Вот то есть
look, uh, 99% that these weren’t Tatars,
смотрите э 99% что это не татары были
they were just Udmurts who lived in
это просто удмурты которые жили в
Tatarstan, yeah, that’s very similar
Татарстане угу вот э это похоже очень
because, uh, your appearance is absolutely
потому что ээ внешность у вас абсолютно
not Tatar if  if there were Tatars in the Rada,
не татарская если бы ээ были в Раду
yes, the thing is that uh,
татары да у вас дело в том что ээ
Asian uh, anthropological, he is
азиатский ээ антропологический п он есть
dominant, if you were, you would definitely
доминирующий если бы были у вас точно
have Asian features, so you would have
были бы черты азиатские так были бы
epicanthus, the shape of your face would be a little
эпикантус форма лица была бы немножко не
different, like this I just saw right away I op
такая вот так Я просто увидел сразу я оп
Udmurt That’s why I immediately asked where
удмурт Я же поэтому и спросил сразу
something came from, that is, most likely
откуда что вот то есть скорее всего у
your ancestors are not Tatars, they are just
вас предки они не татары они просто
Udmurts who lived there in Tatarstan,
удмурты которые в Татарстане жили там ж
but the fact is that in the Volga region there
де в том что на Поволжье очень много
were a lot of different peoples mixed together, so there are
было мешано разных народов так вот есть
Umur settlements, Tatar settlements,
умур поселения татарские поселения
Mari settlements  Chuvash settlements
марийские поселения чувашские поселения
were Yeah, Tatars are also not only in
были Угу татары же тоже не только в
Tatarstan, there are a lot of Tatars there in the lower but Nizhny Novgorod
Татарстане там в нижнем но Нижегородской
region, and in
области татар очень много а в свою
turn, what can you tell about yourself
очередь о себе что вы можете рассказать
about your origins? You probably already
о вашем происхождении Вы наверняка уже
failed my pro of course, yes, because well,
провали моё про конечно да потому что ну
when we study and first year  we must
мы когда учимся да первый курс мы должны
we went through a kind of autoidea, yes, that is,
мы проходили как бы автоидея да то есть
we tried to understand ourselves by our
мы пробовали разбирать себя на своём
example and our diet Yes,
примере и свои рацион Да у
I have mine
меня мои
from the mills of the region from the Poltava region
из мельниц области из Полтавской области
and from the Lugansk region, yes, that is,
и из Луганской области есть да то есть
according to the archival Metrics, they are all Ukrainians,
они по архивным Метрика они все украинцы
so they are all with  these territories
получаются так они все с этих территорий
according to the anthropological type Yes, if
по антропологическом типу Да если вам
this tells you something Yes My type
это что-то говорит Да Мой типаж
belongs to the Di
относится к ди
Nar subtype, don’t say
нарского не говори не
anything Yes, well, I’m weak in the question, so it’s
гово Да ну я слаб в вопросе поэтому
difficult
сложно
But I’ll open another tab for myself
Но я ещё одну вкладок для себя
Di Nar subtype and definitely
открою ди Нарский подтип и обязательно
get to know each other like this Why you  you sit against the background of the flag
знакомлюсь так А почему вы на фоне флага
Well, because if the flag is against the
сидите Ну потому что если флаг будет на
background of me, then you won’t
фоне меня то вы меня не будете
see me. Okay, okay, but you
видеть Хорошо хорошо А вам обязательно у
definitely have some kind of background.
вас наверняка же есть какой-то фон Да на
Besides the flag, why did you decide to
помимо флага почему вы решили именно его
hang it? Well, or not a white cloth there,
повесить Ну или не белую ткань там
for example
например
I decided to hang a
решил повесить
flag, I understood Why I just decided to
флаг я понял А почему просто решил
hang a flag it looks belligerent,
повесить флаг воинственно выглядит
you know, when you meet a person with a
знаете когда встречаешь человека с
flag in the background, it immediately makes you think of something, it’s
флагом на фоне сразу наводит на какие-то
all screwed up when you meet a person
мысли капец это всё встречаешь человека
with curtains in the background Yes, and it makes you
со шторами на фоне Да и наводит на
think of something, well, the curtains are neutral
какие-то мысли не ну шторы ж нейтральная
thing she is
штука она
than in psychology there is such a concept Yes,
чем в психологии есть такое понятие Да
what is an irritant if he teases you Yes, that
что раздражитель если он вас дразнит Да
means you have a problem, for example, well,
значит э проблема у Вас например ну
look, if there is a guy from
намер смотрите вот если там парень из
Belarus there Sees me Yes, he
Беларуси Увидит меня Да он мне ничего
didn’t tell me anything about the flag at all, but the Russians
вообще за флаг не говорил а россияне
say something about the flag  that is, the problem is
что-то говорят за флаг то есть проблема
not in the flag The problem is Who is looking at it
не во флаге Проблема в том Кто на него
So I told you something that is
смотрит Так я вам что-то сказал что
negative. I’m telling you that the problem is this.
негатив Я же говорю что проблема вот это
The Trigger is the name of Noah’s
Триггер так наме
Region in the country at the moment.
обло во в данный момент
Therefore, if it were in the background
страны Поэтому если бы это на фоне был
there was a flag of any other  states
флаг там любого другого государства
that are not currently taking
которые в данный момент не принимает
part in hostilities Well, probably
участие в боевых действиях Ну наверное
Okay, it’s just a person a person posted and I
Окей просто человек человек вывесил а я
think you, as a Ukrainian, cannot help but know
думаю вы как украинец не можете не знать
that your country is currently
что ваша страна в данный момент
taking part in what flag is
принимает участие какой флажок вам
lit for you down there they show near my
светится там внизу показывают возле моей
country when I connected what  same as
страны когда я подключился какой же как
yours in the back Look, this
у вас на заднем Вот вот смотрите это
shows that I’m from Ukraine Yes, it
показывает что я из Украины Да вас это
doesn’t bother you that the Ukrainian flag is lit there
не тревожит что там светится флажок
No, it doesn’t bother you because the
Украины Нет не тревожит потому что это
system identifies you and here you
система идентифицирует вас а здесь вы
have prepared in advance for the preparation, look
заранее подготовили за подгото смотрите
if I’m a person from Ukraine now again
если я человек из Укра сейчас ещё раз
I’ll say right away for a second that I don’t have any
одну секунду сразу скажу у меня нет ни в
negative complaints in any way and it’s
коем случае претензий негатива и
just interesting, look, it’s interesting, I’m a
всего ите интерес смотри интересно вот я
person from Ukraine, I have the flag of my
человек из Украины у меня флаг моей
country, people at football also take the flag of
страны люди на футболе берут тоже флаг
their country Well, that’s normal, people
своей страны Ну это нормально люди
use the flag of their country at different
используют флаг своей страны в разных
moments Yes, why  let's just say I would be too
моментах Да почему вас скажем так я бы я
lazy to go out to
бы поленился для того чтобы выйти
video chat and hang the flag of
видеочат повесить у себя на фоне флаг
my country in the background. It's cool and this is
своей страны Прикольно а это он у меня
hanging at my work because I
на работе висит де в том что я тут
work here and it's always with me. That is, I
работаю и он меня всегда То есть я
probably started this in the wrong way  was the flag
наверное не с того начал этот флаг был
hung in advance or was it hanging there and you
заранее повешен или он висел там и вы
just hung there for a long, long time Yes you promise Okay the
просто давно-давно виси Да обещаете Окей
buzz is cool how how how the situation in you
кайф прикольно как как как ситуация в вы
in Ukraine are currently in
на Украине находитесь в данный момент в
Ukraine in Ukraine in Ukraine Why in
Украине на Украине в Украине Почему в
Ukraine well because we We don’t
Украине ну потому что мы Мы же не
speak
говорим на
Russia, speak
России говорите если
well if you want. Cool, yes, I’m in
хотите хорошо Прикольно да да я в
Ukraine and you’re in
Украине а вы на
Russia, I understand, it’s cool, interesting,
России я да понял прикольно интересно
so I don’t know how things are in Ukraine in Ukraine.
так вот как дела на Украине в на Украине
As a scientist, accuracy is important to you.
знаю Вы вам как учёному важна точность
Yes, the wording, I just look, I
Да формулировок я просто ну смотрите Я
don’t know. Maybe you have  some kind of
не знаю Может у вас есть какой-то там
island of Ukraine and so on we have the
остров Украины и так дальше у нас есть
country Ukraine in Ukraine Uh-huh
страна Украина в Украине Угу
Yes, you are offended when I speak in Ukraine
Да вас обижает когда я говорю на Украине
No, I just don’t quite understand what
Нет я просто не совсем понимаю о чём
you’re talking about in Ukraine, it’s not clear Well, maybe it’s
вы на Украине непонятно Ну может это
some kind of va on the territory of the
какой-то ва на территории на территории
Ukrainian state  Well, like this,
украинского государства Во вот та так
for example, on the territory of the Ukrainian
например на территории украинского
state. It’s clear, otherwise in Ukraine
государства Понятно а то на Украине
Maybe it’s you, some kind of bicycle of
Может это вы какой-то там велосипед
Ukraine. I don’t know the language in Ukraine. Well, it’s
Украины Я не знаю гово на Украи Ну это
in Russian, that’s how we speak in Ukraine.
по-русски вот так мы говорим на Украине
No, look, you may be
Нет смотрите вы вы может неправильно
speaking incorrectly. Well, you don’t  education Why is
говорить Ну вы не образова Почему
it wrong Well, well, well, you understand
неправильно Ну а хорошо Вы же понимаете
there is an official official language and there is a
есть язык официальный официо а есть язык
common people’s language, here in the common people people
простонародный вот в простонародье люди
speak in Ukraine and so, well, look at the
говорят на Украине так вот ну смотрите в
common people with your finger on the butt No
простонародье пальцем попу Нет А
Why don’t I
почему не
want Why don’t you want Why should I
хочу Почему не хотите А почему я должен
want to wipe it once  finger to the butt
хотеть а подтирать когда-то пальцем попу
No, I somehow had at least once in my
Нет у меня как-то было как-то хоть раз в
life that you didn’t have toilet
жизни что у вас не было туалетной
paper and how did you get out of this
бумаги да как вы выкрутились из этого
situation Ravina water the nearest source
положение Равина вода ближайший источник
of water anything Wait I
с водой всё что угодно Подождите В
mean the closest source I’m just
смысле ближай источник Просто мне
interested describe how it is
интересно опишите как это
it was Well, how was it, you don’t have paper
было Ну как это было у тебя нету бумаги
You have Raveena, wash yourself in the
У тебя есть Равина помой себе в
sink in the sink Well, if you don’t have
раковине в раковине Да ну если нет
paper What can you do? And somewhere you
бумаги У тебя что поделать А где-то вы
ended up that there was no shower and there was a
попали что не было душа а была
sink Well, I mean,
раковина Ну я имею в виду
you were a fool somewhere  What was washed in the sink
дура гдето вы были Что вымыли в раковине
unit Well, this is somewhere at the university in a school
узле Ну это гдето в университете в школе
like a house where there is no in some Khrushchev-era building And
типа дома где нет в какой-то хрущёвке А
wait, there was a sink And this
подожди так была раковина А это а душа
was not a shower Well, you don’t know how the Khrushchev-era buildings
не было Ну вы не в курсе да как хрущёвки
are built, they have a separate bathroom for
застроены они с раздельным санузлом у
you  to go out to the shower you
тебя для того чтобы выйти в душ тебе
need to open the door go into the next
надо открыть дверь зайти в соседнюю
room and there will be a shower or a van
комнату и вот там будет душ или ван
then Toilet without a sink the sink is right
то Унитаз без раковины раковина как раз
where Do not I don’t know, maybe it
там где Ду не я не знаю ну там может это
was some kind of modern renovation I
какой-то был современный ремонт была
understood that is, it’s Khrushchev I’m just  I know
понял то есть это хрущёвка я просто знаю
what kind of
какие в
toilets there are in Khrushchev-era buildings. There’s just
хрущёвках туалеты Там просто место
not enough space at all. There’s a sink. It’s such a
вообще мало там раковина Вот такая вот
small one. It’s a small little
маленькая такая вот маленькая маленькая
sink. It’s called a washstand, and that’s
раковина рукомойник это называется и вот
where you come and wash the
там приходи помой
washstand. I’m
рукомойник А какой ваш рост мне
interested in your height. I’m short. I don’t know
интересно у меня низкий рост Я не знаю
how much, 175 maybe. I’m 168.  I’m the one who’s
сколько 175 может Вот у меня 168 Это я
short You’re still a little taller, but
низкий Вы ещё чуть больше но всё равно
I’m still wondering how you got to this
мне интересно как вы достали до этого
washbasin, well, how do you
рукомойника ну как
mean, how did you get
это смысле как достали
it on the level of well, plus or minus, not
онн на уровне ж плюс-минус не
washstands, not on them, at the level of the breasts
рукомойники не на они на уровне грудей
somewhere,
где-то
always not on the level, no, not at all
всегда не на уровне нет нени в коем
case, you have a sink at the level of your breasts at
случае У вас раковина на уровне грудей
home
дома
at the level of the zani, well, just a little there
на уровне зани это что ну чуть-чуть там
at waist level, roughly
на уровне пояса грубо
speaking, so okay, let’s say that is,
говоря так хорошо допустим то есть
wait, you want to say you want to say
подожди хочешь сказать вы хотите сказать
that you have Okay, come on, yes Naro Okay,
что у вас вот Хорошо давай да Наро Ладно
at waist level, but you don’t care  you
на уровне пояса но тебе всё равно
need to lift your ass somehow, like you
задницу надо как-то поднять как ты её
lifted it, you need to lift it a little, but what can you do? How did
поднял немножко надо да что поделать А
you lift it, how did you lift your ass, did you sit
как ты её как ты поднял задницу ты сел
on it? Well, I just can’t understand. How is
на это Ну я просто не могу понять Как
it physically? Well, how are you trying to dodge there
это физически Ну как ты пытаешься там
little by little, it turns out, well, next
потихоньку про получается ну в следующий
time for sure  I’ll record a video I’ll
раз обязательно видео запишу Я
be sure to send it If the details are
обязательно отправлю Если подробности
interesting to you, when
интересны это тебе у у вас когда
did you run out of toilet paper in the bathroom,
заканчивалась туалетная бумага в санузле
how did you cope? I mean, in short, it would be
вы как справлялись я что [__] короче б
shorter to talk about such topics, and you’re
на такие темы общаться короче а вам
ashamed of this, I’m
стыдно об это я
sorry because in
гор потому
Ukraine, the
Украине в
nearest source of water is in the sink, I can immediately
раковине ближайший источник воды я сразу
visualize
визуализировать
[  laughter]
[смех]
on my Telegram directly at once ovin and
на мий Telegram прям зараз овин а
popk tse more and more respectfully YouTube keeping
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg Orcs in your ba
нас через скарг Орки в твый ба
and even more richly video I won’t show people
и дуже багато вдео не показу людям
immediately don’t show information about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стрими
For this purpose, for this purpose, we Mali have an operational
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативний
link to write directly at the same time  there in
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegra okm vdeo shche tezh tsikava and korisna
телегра окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and mi vinni z you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
we will show YouTube Glory to
незалежно того покажем YouTube Слава
Ukraine subscribe
Украине подпишись